douglas-budget.com 2018-06-09

# Privacy Policy | Site | douglas-budget.com

TOU/PP are for both Douglas-Budget & Glen Rock sites.

Terms and Services

 **ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS**

The Douglas Budget provides the web pages available at douglas-budget.com to the general public pursuant to these Terms of Services. These terms may be changed at any time without notice and your continued use of the douglas-budget.com binds you to these changes. If you do not agree to these Terms of Service, do not use douglas-budget.com

 **USER CONTENT**

When you submit to douglas-budget.com, you retain sole ownership of any comments, images, video, audio or other communications or content you submit through the user content service. However, when you contribute, you are granting The Douglas Budget and its designees an irrevocable, royalty-free, worldwide right and license to use such content in perpetuity.  By submitting user content, you are the warranting that you are the sole author or that you have obtained all necessary permissions associated with copyrights, trademarks, rights of publicity and/ or rights of privacy to submit such content. The Douglas Budget monitors all content submitted to the web and retains the right to remove any user content it deems inappropriate.

 **PRIVACY POLICY**

The Douglas Budget and douglas-budget.com and their designees protect your personal information according to this policy. But you understand and agree that by using this service you are not anonymous and the material you submit is not private. The Douglas Budget reserves the right to cooperate and share information with law enforcement officials or third parties in limited circumstances, when complying with legal action or other limited circumstances such as personal attacks or threats. In addition, The Douglas Budget takes reasonable steps to protect the privacy and security of information transmitted between browsers and our server, but shall not be responsible for information which is intercepted in the process. The Douglas Budget also does not knowingly collect any personal data from personal data from persons under 13 years of age, nor does it knowingly allow others to collect that information. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not submit to douglas-budget.com without parental consent. If you wish to protect your privacy and security, do not use e-mail or douglas-budget.com to communicate information you wish to be kept confidential and secure.

 **COPYRIGHT AND PERMISSION RULES**

All materials appearing on douglas-budget.com other than materials submitted under User Content, are protected by copyright under U.S. Copyright and other laws. The materials are the property of The Douglas Budget or the party credited as the provider of the material and copying, reproducing, distributing, publishing, displaying, modifying, transmitting, selling or offering for sale, without the expressed, written permission from The Douglas Budget or the copyright holder is prohibited.

 **USER CONDUCT**

Your right to use douglas-budget.com is subject to be ended at anytime if The Douglas Budget or it designees determines in its sole judgment, that the user content you have transmitted may be illegal or offensive or might violate the rights, harm or threaten the safety of others or in anyway violate these terms of service.

A partial list of the kind of User Content that is prohibited will include but is not limited to:

•Threats to another person or personal attacks or harassment of another person.

•Advertisements or materials deemed as solicitation materials.

•Profane or pronographic material.

•Information that you know to be untrue or misleading.

•Material which promotes illegal activities.

•Material which is potentially libelous

•Material which is discriminatory on account of race, religion, disabilities, sexual orientation or in any other way abusive or discriminatory.

•Falsely misrepresenting another person or entity or your affiliation with that person or entity or impersonating another person or material which may invade another person's privacy.

•Material which infringes on copyrights, trademarks, patents or any other proprietary right of any party.

 **SECURE ACCESS**

While The Douglas Budget intends to make every effort to guarantee continuous and secure access to douglas-budget.com, that access is not a guaranteed right. Nor is the accuracy of the information on douglas-budget.com guaranteed. Rely on any materials (including but not limited to the User Content) at your own risk. If you are dissatisfied with any portion of douglas-budget.com, your only and exclusive remedy is to discontinue the use of douglas-budget.com.

 **ABOUT THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you use our Services. If so, a list of these ad serving companies will be available here. These companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to our sites or use of our Services and to other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.<br>

These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message).

We encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the [**Network Advertising Initiative's**](https://www.networkadvertising.org/) consumer website.

Google Doubleclick for Publishers (DFP) is an ad network partner that displays ads on our Services. To improve your ad experience on our sites and Services and elsewhere on the Internet, we may send non-personal information to Google DFP based on your browser's activities, such as type of pages viewed and categories of interests, so that the advertising you see is relevant to you.

Google DFP also may use information regarding its own users to select which ads to display. [**Click here**](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) to learn more about Google DFP's ad practices, including how to opt out of using anonymous information to select which ads to show you.

 **OPT-OUT OF COOKIES**

If you wish to manage or opt-out of cookies utilized by our site and third party advertisers, you can take the following steps:

You may be able to download an opt-out cookie from the third party advertiser's website allowing you to opt-out of cookies. Please visit the third party advertiser's websites for more information.

• Your web browser may allow you to manage what cookies are accepted or declined. These settings can usually be found in the preferences or options menus of your web browser.

• Your web browser may also allow you to manually view cookies and delete the cookies you don't want or need. Check your web browser's settings for more information.

• Websites that require registration may allow you to opt-out of cookies. Check the account settings or preferences section of the website for more information.

For more information, please visit [**http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)
